{"data":[{"question":"Most school-leavers have the ________ to go to work because they want to live independently.","a":"keen","b":"keenly","c":"keenness","d":"keener","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The + Noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"________ objections to the plan haven't happened.","a":"Expectant","b":"Expected","c":"Expect","d":"Expectation","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adjective (expected) usually goes before the noun they modify\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Many students are so afraid ________ failing that they deny all invitations.","a":"at","b":"about","c":"to","d":"of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be afraid of something\/ doing something: worried that something bad might happen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"It is important that the TOEFL office ________ an applicant's registration.","a":"will confirm","b":"confirm","c":"confirms","d":"must confirm","answer":"2","explain":"\n- \u00a0Suggest is followed by a that-clause in which the subjunctive is used (It's important that somebody do something)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Please state your name, age and ________.","a":"occupied (v)","b":"occupied (adj)","c":"occupation","d":"occupational","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use parallel structure with nouns","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Deserts are often formed ________ they are cut off from rain-bearing winds by the surrounding mountain ranges.","a":"because","b":"in spite of","c":"so","d":"due to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Because + Clause: give the reason to do something.\u00a0\n- In spite of\/due to: + noun\/noun phrase.\n- So: used to say that someone does something because of the reason just stated.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"________ that the English settled in Jamestown.","a":"In 1607 that it was","b":"That in 1607","c":"Because in 1607","d":"It was in 1607","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It's + in year\/month\/date... that.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Staying in a hotel costs ________ renting a room in a dormitory for a week.","a":"twice more than","b":"twice as much as","c":"as much twice as","d":"as much as twice","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Twice\/ double + as + adjective\/adverb + as.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"When friends insist on ________ expensive gifts, it makes most Americans uncomfortable.","a":"them to accept","b":"their accepting","c":"they accepting","d":"they accept","answer":"2","explain":"- Insist on one's V-ing \u00a0= someone insists on doing something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Do any of these designs ________ you?","a":"attract","b":"attractive","c":"attractiveness","d":"attractively","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sentence structure: S+ V+O.\u00a0\n+ Question: Auxi (do\/does\/did\/will\/is...) + S + V + O.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}